<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<FAQ>
  <TitleEn>ORION FAQs</TitleEn>
  <TitleAr>الأسئلة الشائعة حول أورايون</TitleAr>
  <FAQdata>
    <ENTitle>ORION FAQs</ENTitle>
    <ARTitle>الأسئلة الشائعة حول أورايون</ARTitle>
  <ENQ>What are Orion’s services?</ENQ>
  <ARQ>ما هي خدمات أورايون؟</ARQ>
      <ENA>
        Orion is a fully integrated services platform that offers you whatever service you need through our network of service providers and through Orion itself.
        Orion is a cost-efficient solution as we provide the same services from the service providers but at a lower cost.
        For more details on our offerings, please check our services page for our full range of services and their prices.
      </ENA>
      <ARA>
        أورايون عبارة عن منصة خدمات متكاملة تمامًا تقدم لك أي خدمة تحتاجها من خلال شبكة مزودي الخدمة لدينا ومن خلال أورايون نفسها.
        أورايون هو حل فعال من حيث التكلفة حيث نقدم نفس الخدمات من مزودي الخدمة ولكن بتكلفة أقل.
        لمزيد من التفاصيل حول عروضنا، يرجى مراجعة صفحة خدماتنا لمعرفة المجموعة الكاملة من الخدمات وأسعارها.
      </ARA>
  </FAQdata>

  <FAQdata>
    <ENTitle>ORION FAQs</ENTitle>
    <ARTitle>الأسئلة الشائعة حول أورايون</ARTitle>
    <ENQ>How to book a service? </ENQ>
    <ARQ>كيف تحجز الخدمة؟</ARQ>
      <ENA>
        For a seamless booking, pick the service you need from our services page and call us on 16286 to make the reservation.
        For more details on our offerings, please check our services page for our full range of services and their prices.
      </ENA>
      <ARA>
        لحجز سلس، اختر الخدمة التي تحتاجها من صفحة خدماتنا واتصل بنا على 16286 لإجراء الحجز.
        لمزيد من التفاصيل حول عروضنا، يرجى مراجعة صفحة خدماتنا لمعرفة المجموعة الكاملة من الخدمات وأسعارها.
      </ARA>
  </FAQdata>

  <FAQdata>
    <ENTitle>ORION FAQs</ENTitle>
    <ARTitle>الأسئلة الشائعة حول أورايون</ARTitle>
    <ENQ>How much do our services cost?</ENQ>
    <ARQ>كم تكلفة خدماتنا؟</ARQ>
    <ENA>
        You can check our services page for our full range of services and their prices
        You can also call us on 16286 or chat with us through WhatsApp on the number 01101016286.
      </ENA>
    <ARA>
        يمكنك التحقق من صفحة خدماتنا لمعرفة المجموعة الكاملة من الخدمات ثم الاتصال بنا على 16286 لمزيد من التفاصيل أوتواصل معنا عبر خدمة الواتس آب على الرقم 01101016286
      </ARA>
  </FAQdata>

  <FAQdata>
    <ENTitle>ORION FAQs</ENTitle>
    <ARTitle>الأسئلة الشائعة حول أورايون</ARTitle>
    <ENQ>What areas does Orion cover?</ENQ>
    <ARQ>ما هي المناطق التي تغطيها أورايون؟</ARQ>
    <ENA>
        Orion offers its services in Madinaty, Rehab, 5th, 3rd, and 1st Settlement, and El Shrouk city.
      </ENA>
    <ENA>
        تقدم أورايون خدماتها في مدينتي ، الرحاب ، التجمع الخامس ، الثالث ، الأول ومدينة الشروق.
      </ENA>
    </FAQdata>

  <FAQdata>
    <ENTitle>ORION FAQs</ENTitle>
    <ARTitle>الأسئلة الشائعة حول أورايون</ARTitle>
    <ENQ>Who are the service providers/partners network?</ENQ>
    <ARQ>من هم مزودو الخدمة / شبكة الشركاء؟</ARQ>
    <ENA>
        We have a wide network of service providers tailored to meet all your needs. You can check our Partners page to check the full list.
        For more details and bookings, please call us on 16286 or chat with us through WhatsApp on the number 01101016286
      </ENA>
    <ENA>
        لدينا شبكة واسعة من مزودي الخدمة المصممين لتلبية جميع احتياجاتك. يمكنك مراجعة صفحة شركائنا للتحقق من القائمة الكاملة
        لمزيد من التفاصيل والحجوزات ، يرجى الاتصال بنا على 16286 أو التواصل معنا على الواتس آب على الرقم 01101016286
      </ENA>
  </FAQdata>
</FAQ>
